[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["fox", "dog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["jackal", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["goose", "zebra"]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["llama", "cow"]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["squirrel", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["donkey", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["goat", "antelope"]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["antelope", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["duck", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["goose", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["goose", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "cow"]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["llama", "sheep"]
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["antelope", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "jackal"]
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "dog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["jackal", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["beaver", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["antelope", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "goose"]
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["mouse", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "sheep"]
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["fox", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "dog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["fox", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "crocodile"]
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["frog", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["squirrel", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["antelope", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["dog", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "goose"]
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "cow"]
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["squirrel", "beaver"]
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["frog", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "frog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["dog", "fox"]
    }
]
